We're talking about how to make an easy and unique centerpiece.
For your table, for any party.
Now every party has a theme.
And it doesn't necessarily have to be like an obvious theme.
Like, this theme is a patriotic theme.
Or this hat you could use for a St Patrick's Day party.
But even if you don't have something like that.
You're just wanting to throw a party.
And you want something to look like just elegant or classy.
Or just fun.
You can use this centerpiece idea for anything.
So we can start with just a plain hat and build on from there.
Or we can start with, even party hats.
And these type of hats can be used for.
If you're having a soccer birthday party.
Or if you're having a soccer party, like your soccer team just won a championship.
And you need an idea for a centerpiece.
You can use a hat like this, too.